Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1982 May-1982 June; DVD (Disc 24)
    - Plugging government program loopholes, 1982 May 25 (Video 25)
    - Commencement, 1982 May 26 (Video 26)
    - Some europeans dislike America, 1982 May 27 (Video 27)
    - Correcting food stamp abuses, 1982 May 28 (Video 28)
    - Falklands crisis is our crisis, 1982 May 29 (Video 29)
    - People lose in budget battle, 1982 May 30 (Video 30)
    - Support Simpson immigration bill, 1982 May 31 (Video 31)
    - Another point of view - Evan Bybee, re Falkland War, 1982 June 1 (Video 32)
    - School board favoritism, 1982 June 2 (Video 33)
    - Change needed in naval strategy, 1982 June 3 (Video 34)
    - Balanced budget amendment will pass, 1982 June 4 (Video 35)
    - The world has changed, 1982 June 5 (Video 36)
    - Senator Garn's welcome outburst, 1982 June 6 (Video 37)
    - Reduce annual drowning loss, 1982 June 7 (Video 38)
    - Special needs of the handicapped, 1982 June 8 (Video 39)
    - Building industry gets help, 1982 June 9 (Video 40)
    - Thinking the unthinkable, 1982 June 10 (Video 41)
    - The artificial heart question, 1982 June 11 (Video 42)
    - Community needs and problems, 1982 June 12 (Video 43)
    - No insurance, no driving, 1982 June 13 (Video 44)
    - Scenario for utility service, 1982 June 14 (Video 45)
    - Room tax deserves support, 1982 June 15 (Video 46)
    - County studies cable regulation, 1982 June 16 (Video 47)
    - High schools adopt soccer, 1982 June 17 (Video 48)
    - A work of art, 1982 June 18 (Video 49)
    - Protectionism is no answer, 1982 June 19 (Video 50)
    - Anniversary of a symbol, 1982 June 20 (Video 51)
    - More trouble in the mideast, 1982 June 21 (Video 52)
    - University strengthens admission policy, 1982 June 22 (Video 53)
    - Voters reject negative appeals, 1982 June 23 (Video 54)
    - School on alcoholism and drugs, 1982 June 24 (Video 55)
    - Videotapes and copyrights, 1982 June 25 (Video 56)
    - Bad news or more news, 1982 June 26 (Video 57)
    - Benefits of plea bargaining, 1982 June 27 (Video 58)
    - Crime on the streets, 1982 June 28 (Video 59)
    - Tax shelter burn-out, 1982 June 29 (Video 60)
    - Why editorials?, 1982 June 30 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1982 July-1982 August; DVD (Disc 25)
    - Filing date for school boards, 1982 July 1 (Video 1)
    - Change the pipeline decision, 1982 July 2 (Video 2)
    - Improve the State Department, 1982 July 3 (Video 3)
    - "The people shall say 'amen'", 1982 July 4 (Video 4)
    - Ban the brine flies, 1982 July 5 (Video 5)
    - Finding creative solutions, 1982 July 6 (Video 6)
    - Another point of view - Commissioner Doug Green, re Navy ships, 1982 July 7 (Video 7)
    - Politics and Triad center, 1982 July 8 (Video 8)
    - The Hinckley verdict, 1982 July 9 (Video 9)
    - Next problem in the mideast, 1982 July 10 (Video 10)
    - Terrorism and drunk driving, 1982 July 11 (Video 11)
    - Youth gangs pose danger, 1982 July 12 (Video 12)
    - Another point of view - Ilene Kamsler, re hotel taxes, 1982 July 13 (Video 13)
    - Constitutional end run, 1982 July 14 (Video 14)
    - Convene legislature in Emery county, 1982 July 15 (Video 15)
    - Flat rate tax attractive, 1981 July 16 (Video 16)
    - Pornography laws are changing, 1982 July 17 (Video 17)
    - Easing the stress of unemployment, 1982 July 18 (Video 18)
    - Housing market in turmoil, 1982 July 19 (Video 19)
    - Another point of view - Rep. Mac Haddow, re social services, 1982 July 20 (Video 20)
    - EPA rules need updating, 1982 July 21 (Video 21)
    - Another point of view - Francis Woods, re crime, 1982 July 22 (Video 22)
    - The stories not reported, 1982 July 23 (Video 23)
    - The pioneer character, 1982 July 24 (Video 24)
    - More advice on diet, 1982 July 25 (Video 25)
    - Don't permit street vendors, 1982 July 26 (Video 26)
    - Another point of view - Rep. John E. Smith, re plea bargaining, 1982 July 27 (Video 27)
    - Fighting neighborhood blight, 1982 July 28 (Video 28)
    - Come out fighting, but..., 1982 July 29 (Video 29)
    - Thrift company loss not threat, 1982 July 30 (Video 30)
    - Let's talk to the PLO, 1982 July 31 (Video 31)
    - The treasure of expectation, 1982 August 1 (Video 32)
    - Key to balanced budget amendment, 1982 August 2 (Video 33)
    - Another point of view - Ron Simpson, re copyright, 1982 August 3 (Video 34)
    - End fireworks confusion, 1982 August 4 (Video 35)
    - Spotlight on drinking drivers, 1982 August 5 (Video 36)
    - Approve legislative pay changes, 1982 August 6 (Video 37)
    - Tuition tax credits ill-advised, 1982 August 7 (Video 38)
    - Facts abotu "big" government, 1982 August 8 (Video 39)
    - Business week, 1982 August 9 (Video 40)
    - Another point of view - Linda Reeder, 1982 August 10 (Video 41)
    - A vote for the partners, 1982 August 11 (Video 42)
    - Progress on nuclear waste policy, 1982 August 12 (Video 43)
    - Support rule-breaking tax bill (not recorded for archive), 1982 August 13 (Video 44)
    - Rule change needed on herpes, 1982 August 14 (Video 45)
    - The cost of unemployment, 1982 August 15 (Video 46)
    - Court ruling doomed to fail, 1982 August 16 (Video 47)
    - Another point of view - Bill Chinn, re rate increases, 1982 August 17 (Video 48)
    - The personality of a city, 1982 August 18 (Video 49)
    - The value of imagination, 1982 August 19 (Video 50)
    - Those frightening statistics, 1982 August 20 (Video 51)
    - Student aid not critical, 1982 August 21 (Video 52)
    - The role of government, 1982 August 22 (Video 53)
    - American institute of applied politics, 1982 August 23 (Video 54)
    - Another point of view - Walt Lichfield, 1982 August 24 (Video 55)
    - Football players threaten strike, 1982 August 25 (Video 56)
    - Homes for mentally retarded, 1982 August 26 (Video 57)
    - Guest editorials, 1982 August 27 (Video 58)
    - Experience for the handicapped, 1982 August 28 (Video 59)
    - Trade: prescription for peace?, 1982 August 29 (Video 60)
    - School days, school days, 1982 August 30 (Video 61)
    - Bureaucrats and indians, 1982 August 31 (Video 62)
  - KSL editorials, 1982 September-1982 October; DVD (Disc 26)
    - KSL-CBS golden anniversary (not recorded for archive), 1982 September 1 (Video 1)
    - How to reduce obesity (not recorded for archive), 1982 September 2 (Video 2)
    - A child is born, 1982 September 3 (Video 3)
    - Revolution in money markets, 1982 September 4 (Video 4)
    - Americans well informed, but..., 1982 September 5 (Video 5)
    - The tax load in Utah, 1982 September 6 (Video 6)
    - Another point of view - Steven Jones, re unemployment, 1982 September 7 (Video 7)
    - Public meetings are open meetings, 1982 September 8 (Video 8)
    - Another vote for marriage, 1982 September 9 (Video 9)
    - Changes needed for PSC, 1982 September 10 (Video 10)
    - End delay on asbestos problem, 1982 September 11 (Video 11)
    - Support mideast peace plan, 1982 September 12 (Video 12)
    - Emigration visitors district, 1982 September 13 (Video 13)
    - Another point of view - Gordon Lind, re brine flies, 1982 September 14 (Video 14)
    - Make Hogle Zoo a state park, 1982 September 15 (Video 15)
    - Another point of view - Grant Buma, re tax loopholes, 1981 September 16 (Video 16)
    - Nuclear energy still the answer, 1982 September 17 (Video 17)
    - Child identification plan, 1982 September 18 (Video 18)
    - Science education needs emphasis, 1982 September 19 (Video 19)
    - Study school board races, 1982 September 20 (Video 20)
    - Another point of view - Mike Sibbett, re cattle grazing, 1982 September 21 (Video 21)
    - Salt Lake streets improving, 1982 September 22 (Video 22)
    - The value of advertising, 1982 September 23 (Video 23)
    - Study constitutional amendments, 1982 September 24 (Video 24)
    - Why government programs fail, 1982 September 25 (Video 25)
    - Courts must remain independent, 1982 September 26 (Video 26)
    - United way is the fair way, 1982 September 27 (Video 27)
    - Don't be fooled by facts, 1982 September 28 (Video 28)
    - More misleading facts, 1982 September 29 (Video 29)
    - Mexico needs realistic response, 1982 September 30 (Video 30)
    - Racism ugly in any form, 1982 October 1 (Video 31)
    - Watch trend in oil supply, 1982 October 2 (Video 32)
    - History and the football strike, 1982 October 3 (Video 33)
    - Remember school bus laws, 1982 October 4 (Video 34)
    - Tax article revision, 1982 October 5 (Video 35)
    - Trade fantasy for numbers, 1982 October 6 (Video 36)
    - Time for a "peace academy", 1982 October 7 (Video 37)
    - Lessons from the flood, 1982 October 8 (Video 38)
    - Blame it on El Chicon, 1982 October 9 (Video 39)
    - An attack on trust, 1982 October 10 (Video 40)
    - Legislative compensation, 1982 October 11 (Video 41)
    - Another point of view - Lyman Kunz, re the constitution, 1982 October 12 (Video 42)
    - Thanks to flood volunteers, 1982 October 13 (Video 43)
    - Slow redevelopment agencies, 1982 October 14 (Video 44)
    - Changes in unemployment program, 1982 October 15 (Video 45)
    - Legislative residency requirement, 1982 October 16 (Video 46)
    - Criminal justice steering committee, 1982 October 17 (Video 47)
    - Tax laws encourage mistakes, 1982 October 18 (Video 48)
    - Another point of view - Rep. Frank Knowlton, re proposition one, 1982 October 19 (Video 49)
    - Another point of view - Dale Zabriskie, re proposition one, 1982 October 20 (Video 50)
    - Nuclear waste storage safety, 1982 October 21 (Video 51)
    - Welcome to American Express, 1982 October 22 (Video 52)
    - Twenty years of editorials, 1982 October 23 (Video 53)
    - A troubled United Nations, 1982 October 24 (Video 54)
    - Proposition four - corporate officers, 1982 October 25 (Video 55)
    - Congratulations to Senator Garn, 1982 October 26 (Video 56)
    - Utah voter information pamphlet, 1982 October 27 (Video 57)
    - Prepare for a tough winter, 1982 October 28 (Video 58)
    - Make it a safe halloween, 1982 October 29 (Video 59)
    - Unemployment means changes, 1982 October 30 (Video 60)
    - Encourage cultural exchanges, 1982 October 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1982 November-1982 December; DVD (Disc 27)
    - Vote tomorrow, 1982 November 1 (Video 1)
    - Compensation for the victims, 1982 November 2 (Video 2)
    - Changes needed in campaigning, 1982 November 3 (Video 3)
    - Support child seat belt rule, 1982 November 4 (Video 4)
    - Reality and the kidnapping scare, 1982 November 5 (Video 5)
    - Election rules penalize broadcasters, 1982 November 6 (Video 6)
    - It's a tough world, 1982 November 7 (Video 7)
    - School standards vote unanimous, 1982 November 8 (Video 8)
    - What next in Lebanon, 1982 November 9 (Video 9)
    - The system encourages dishonesty, 1982 November 10 (Video 10)
    - It's time for catalogs, 1982 November 11 (Video 11)
    - Improve highway marking system, 1982 November 12 (Video 12)
    - "The blue and the gray", 1982 November 13 (Video 13)
    - Education begins with the students, 1982 November 14 (Video 14)
    - Americans and their congress, 1982 November 15 (Video 15)
    - Don't stifle scientific research, 1982 November 16 (Video 16)
    - Renew "certificate of need", 1982 November 17 (Video 17)
    - America's crumbling infrastructure (not recorded for archive), 1982 November 18 (Video 18)
    - Congressional voting records, 1982 November 19 (Video 19)
    - "The business of America", 1982 November 20 (Video 20)
    - Where are we headed?, 1982 November 21 (Video 21)
    - Balanced budget fictions, 1982 November 22 (Video 22)
    - Another point of view - Dev Lanner, re nuclear waste, 1982 November 23 (Video 23)
    - The penalties of illiteracy, 1982 November 24 (Video 24)
    - Thanksgiving, 1982 November 25 (Video 25)
    - Answers to unemployment, 1982 November 26 (Video 26)
    - Exercise in the work place, 1982 November 27 (Video 27)
    - The robots are coming, 1982 November 28 (Video 28)
    - The thirty year miracle, 1982 November 29 (Video 29)
    - The example of Taiwan, 1982 November 30 (Video 30)
    - Lessons from Taiwan, 1982 December 1 (Video 31)
    - Taiwan and the mainland, 1982 December 2 (Video 32)
    - Japan and American ingenuity, 1982 December 3 (Video 33)
    - As easy as 'a,' 'b,' 'c', 1982 December 4 (Video 34)
    - Problems in mainland China, 1982 December 5 (Video 35)
    - Special bond session needed, 1982 December 6 (Video 36)
    - Another point of view - Dr. Lynn Wilcox, re health costs, 1982 December 7 (Video 37)
    - Shoplifter's hand in your pocket, 1982 December 8 (Video 38)
    - Gasoline tax increase needed, 1982 December 9 (Video 39)
    - The promise of young talent, 1982 December 10 (Video 40)
    - The holiday time of Hanukka, 1982 December 11 (Video 41)
    - The robots are coming (see Nov. 28; scheduling mixup) (not recorded for archive), 1982 December 12 (Video 42)
    - Quarters for Christmas, 1982 December 13 (Video 43)
    - Another point of view - Mike Meredith, 1982 December 14 (Video 44)
    - Bound up in books, 1982 December 15 (Video 45)
    - Fact and fantasy about utilities, 1982 December 16 (Video 46)
    - Words for the artifical heart, 1982 December 17 (Video 47)
    - Economy grows, but not enough, 1982 December 18 (Video 48)
    - Where were the snowplows?, 1982 December 19 (Video 49)
    - Holiday driving reminder, 1982 December 20 (Video 50)
    - Another point of view - Kenneth Cox, re highway markers, 1982 December 21 (Video 51)
    - BYU raises entrance requirements, 1982 December 22 (Video 52)
    - No panic over social security, 1982 December 23 (Video 53)
    - Christmas Eve, 1982 December 24 (Video 54)
    - Christmas Day, 1982 December 25 (Video 55)
    - More americans want to work, 1982 December 26 (Video 56)
    - Child restraint law needed, 1982 December 27 (Video 57)
    - Another point of view - Earl Vanfleet, re United Nations, 1982 December 28 (Video 58)
    - Highway safety record, 1982 December 29 (Video 59)
    - Look in the mirror, 1982 December 30 (Video 60)
    - New Year's Eve, 1982 December 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1983 January-1983 February; DVD (Disc 28)
    - New Year's Day, 1983 January 1 (Video 1)
    - Control health care costs, 1983 January 2 (Video 2)
    - The spectacle of congress, 1983 January 3 (Video 3)
    - Postal union over-reacts, 1983 January 4 (Video 4)
    - Drunk drivers are nice people?, 1983 January 5 (Video 5)
    - Happy birthday, maestro, 1983 January 6 (Video 6)
    - Let the defense debate begin, 1983 January 7 (Video 7)
    - Economic growth necessary, 1983 January 8 (Video 8)
    - Turn on the lights!, 1983 January 9 (Video 9)
    - Sandy city and social security, 1983 January 10 (Video 10)
    - Another point of view - drunk driver (in shadow), 1983 January 11 (Video 11)
    - State budget faces problems, 1983 January 12 (Video 12)
    - PAC man and traffic signals, 1983 January 13 (Video 13)
    - Times require flexbility, 1983 January 14 (Video 14)
    - Pity our poor congressman, 1983 January 15 (Video 15)
    - Social security needs adjustment, 1983 January 16 (Video 16)
    - Another point of view - Mayor L. Smith, re social security, 1983 January 17 (Video 17)
    - Teacher appreciation week, 1983 January 18 (Video 18)
    - Another point of view - Stan Wangsgaard, re utility rates, 1983 January 19 (Video 19)
    - Stay away from tariffs, 1983 January 20 (Video 20)
    - Support social security plan, 1983 January 21 (Video 21)
    - Watch for stray joggers, 1983 January 22 (Video 22)
    - Take time to be involved, 1983 January 23 (Video 23)
    - Elected PSC not desirable, 1983 January 24 (Video 24)
    - What good is a zoo?, 1983 January 25 (Video 25)
    - Flood prevention needed now, 1983 January 26 (Video 26)
    - Another point of view - Carl Palmer, re utility rates, 1983 January 27 (Video 27)
    - Change the course, 1983 January 28 (Video 28)
    - The debate over nuclear arms, 1983 January 29 (Video 29)
    - Why americans lose confidence, 1983 January 30 (Video 30)
    - It's a good job, but..., 1983 January 31 (Video 31)
    - Two stories, two philosophies, 1983 February 1 (Video 32)
    - Reality and drug problems, 1983 February 2 (Video 33)
    - Do not dilute vocational colleges, 1983 February 3 (Video 34)
    - Some federal programs work (not recorded for archive), 1983 February 4 (Video 35)
    - Transient merchant bill, 1983 February 5 (Video 36)
    - Courtesy takes a holiday, 1983 February 6 (Video 37)
    - Primary Children's Medical Center, 1983 February 7 (Video 38)
    - Another point of view - Tim Tate, re public employees, 1983 February 8 (Video 39)
    - Elected PSCs and the record, 1983 February 9 (Video 40)
    - Students deserve appreciation, 1983 February 10 (Video 41)
    - Approve veterans cemetery, 1983 February 11 (Video 42)
    - Truck strike was a disgrace, 1983 February 12 (Video 43)
    - You can't legislate intelligence, 1983 February 13 (Video 44)
    - Salt palace lighting needed, 1983 February 14 (Video 45)
    - Another point of view - Senator Brent Overson, re utility rates, 1983 February 15 (Video 46)
    - Solve the zoo problems now, 1983 February 16 (Video 47)
    - Law enforcement costs money, 1983 February 17 (Video 48)
    - Health care needs competition, 1983 February 18 (Video 49)
    - Highway spill on Beck Street, 1983 February 19 (Video 50)
    - Local taxes and the legislature, 1983 February 20 (Video 51)
    - SUSC special events center, 1983 February 21 (Video 52)
    - Another point of view - Lisa Robertson, re teacher salaries, 1983 February 22 (Video 53)
    - The limits of economy, 1983 February 23 (Video 54)
    - Trout stamp a necessary evil, 1983 February 24 (Video 55)
    - Another point of view - Dr. George Middleton, 1983 February 25 (Video 56)
    - The story of two "leaks", 1983 February 26 (Video 57)
    - Beware of fraudulent schemes, 1983 February 27 (Video 58)
    - Stop abuse by redevelopment agencies, 1983 February 28 (Video 59)
  - KSL editorials, 1983 March-1983 April; DVD (Disc 29)
    - Another point of view - Michael Casey, 1983 March 1 (Video 1)
    - Deficit threatens recovery, 1983 March 2 (Video 2)
    - Inter-tribal indian school, 1983 March 3 (Video 3)
    - Another point of view - Dr. Jonathan Horne, re health care, 1983 March 4 (Video 4)
    - Increase the severance tax, 1983 March 5 (Video 5)
    - Time to lower interest rates, 1983 March 6 (Video 6)
    - Tax commission reorganization, 1983 March 7 (Video 7)
    - Another point of view - Dr. Arvo Van Alstyne, re vocational colleges, 1983 March 8 (Video 8)
    - General Motors and Toyota, 1983 March 9 (Video 9)
    - Oil price decline creates problems, 1983 March 10 (Video 10)
    - Legislature sets the agenda, 1983 March 11 (Video 11)
    - Good news about economy, 1983 March 12 (Video 12)
    - Measuring the generosity factor, 1983 March 13 (Video 13)
    - Utility regulation and legislature, 1983 March 14 (Video 14)
    - Another poitn of view - George Tanner, re vocational education, 1983 March 15 (Video 15)
    - Freedom of information day, 1983 March 16 (Video 16)
    - Recall tax study commission, 1983 March 17 (Video 17)
    - National energy education day, 1983 March 18 (Video 18)
    - Written standards correct confusion, 1983 March 19 (Video 19)
    - The benefits of travel, 1983 March 20 (Video 20)
    - Drug abuse on the increase, 1983 March 21 (Video 21)
    - Letters from vocational students, 1983 March 22 (Video 22)
    - Secrets of traffic control, 1983 March 23 (Video 23)
    - Justice coordination wins approval, 1983 March 24 (Video 24)
    - Farmers are the heroes, 1983 March 25 (Video 25)
    - Cameras in the senate gallery, 1983 March 26 (Video 26)
    - Survival of a free society, 1983 March 27 (Video 27)
    - El Salvador has suffered enough, 1983 March 28 (Video 28)
    - Another point of view - Myron Nelson, 1983 March 29 (Video 29)
    - Environmental protection needed, 1983 March 30 (Video 30)
    - More facts about utilities, 1983 March 31 (Video 31)
    - More about the Plandome Hotel, 1983 April 1 (Video 32)
    - Job training partnership act, 1983 April 2 (Video 33)
    - Easter sunday, 1983 April 3 (Video 34)
    - Legalized gambling not the answer, 1983 April 4 (Video 35)
    - Teen driving record attacked, 1983 April 5 (Video 36)
    - The law of cause and effect, 1983 April 6 (Video 37)
    - Peace is the first priority, 1983 April 7 (Video 38)
    - Mistaken rule on pediatric care, 1983 April 8 (Video 39)
    - The nobility of peace, 1983 April 9 (Video 40)
    - Airport security devices senseless, 1983 April 10 (Video 41)
    - Indians trying to adjust, 1983 April 11 (Video 42)
    - DOE makes amends, 1983 April 12 (Video 43)
    - Spring is here, 1983 April 13 (Video 44)
    - Government jobs not for utahns, 1983 April 14 (Video 45)
    - Annual day of reckoning, 1983 April 15 (Video 46)
    - Chinese tennis star becomes a symbol, 1983 April 16 (Video 47)
    - Guard against inferiority complex, 1983 April 17 (Video 48)
    - Jerry Pimm - gentlemen coach, 1983 April 18 (Video 49)
    - Another point of view - S. Val Staker, re road paving, 1983 April 19 (Video 50)
    - Behind every chuckhole..., 1983 April 20 (Video 51)
    - Ririe-Woodbury dancers to China, 1983 April 21 (Video 52)
    - Law prohiits Nicaragua interference, 1983 April 22 (Video 53)
    - Why business owners go gray, 1983 April 23 (Video 54)
    - "Blessed are the peacemakers", 1983 April 24 (Video 55)
    - Leonardo Da Vinci, 1983 April 25 (Video 56)
    - Another poitn of view - Cordell Anderson, 1983 April 26 (Video 57)
    - Hooray for UP&L Workers, 1983 April 27 (Video 58)
    - Another point of view - Terry Holzworth, 1983 April 28 (Video 59)
    - Here's one for the zipper, 1983 April 29 (Video 60)
    - Video recorders and copyright, 1983 April 30 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1983 May-1983 June; DVD (Disc 30)
    - Lebanon problem difficult to solve, 1983 May 1 (Video 1)
    - Gandhi's seven deadly sins, 1983 May 2 (Video 2)
    - Another point of view - Lee Allen, 1983 May 3 (Video 3)
    - UP&L seeks low-cost power, 1983 May 4 (Video 4)
    - Another point of view - Jack Smith, re gambling in Utah, 1983 May 5 (Video 5)
    - Commission on education excellence, 1983 May 6 (Video 6)
    - Television gets a "bad rap", 1983 May 7 (Video 7)
    - Mother's Day, 1983 May 8 (Video 8)
    - Don't worry about youngsters, 1983 May 9 (Video 9)
    - Another point of view - Sen. Glade Sowards, 1983 May 10 (Video 10)
    - Local option tax a necessity, 1983 May 11 (Video 11)
    - Minimum-security work camp, 1983 May 12 (Video 12)
    - Asking the wrong question, 1983 May 13 (Video 13)
    - Cooperation at Thistle Junction, 1983 May 14 (Video 14)
    - Boredom is the prison..., 1983 May 15 (Video 15)
    - Attracting "high tech" industry, 1983 May 16 (Video 16)
    - Another point of view - Terry Lloyd, re tax structure, 1983 May 17 (Video 17)
    - Flood control efforts appreciated, 1983 May 18 (Video 18)
    - Hansen planetarium in danger, 1983 May 19 (Video 19)
    - Farmers set an example, 1983 May 20 (Video 20)
    - Draft regis. and student loans, 1983 May 21 (Video 21)
    - Business has problems, too (not recorded for archive), 1983 May 22 (Video 22)
    - Tip tax heralds tipless table (not recorded for archive), 1983 May 23 (Video 23)
    - Another point of view - Bill Adams (not recorded for archive), 1983 May 24 (Video 24)
    - Time to coordinate street signs (not recorded for archive), 1983 May 25 (Video 25)